Guide to the Sir William Wiseman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- BUSINESS AND PERSONAL, 1917-1961; Series III; 3.25 linear feet (8 boxes)
  - Select Correspondence
    - Klein, Julius, 1930, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Knowlton, Hugh, (*), 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Kuhn, Loeb, & Company, (*), 1928, 1954-1957 (Box 16, Folder 68-69)
    - Legorreta, Luis G., (*), 1948-1960 (Box 16, Folder 70-72)
    - Lloyd, Geoffrey, (*), 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Martin, Janet, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, 1958 April - May (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Mexican Gulf Sulphur Company, (*), 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 75-76)
    - Morris & McVeigh, (*), 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 77-78)
    - Nigeria, Economic Mission, from the Western Region of, (* ), 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - North British Rubber Company, 1956 April, 1958 March - April (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Oakes, Lady Eunice, (*), 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Photocolor Process Corporation, (*), 1945-1952 (Box 17, Folder 82-100)
    - Rainsford-Hannay, Ramsay and Margaret (Wiseman), (* ), 1946-1959, undated (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Reading, Gerald R. Isaacs, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Reynolds Metals Company, (*), 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 103-104)
    - Schiff, John Mortimer, (*), 1941-1960 (Box 18, Folder 105-114)
    - Seymour, Charles, (*), 1922-1960 (Box 18, Folder 115-116)
    - Society of the Friends of English Harbour, Antigua, (* ), 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 117-118)
    - Stephenson, William S., (*), 1956-1961 (Box 18, Folder 119-121)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1959 September - October (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Strauss, Lewis L., (*), 1945-1960, undated (Box 18, Folder 123-128)
    - Storey, Eustace, (*), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - Stroock & Stroock & Lavan, (* ), 1958-1961 (Box 18, Folder 130)
    - Sturridge, Maureen, (*), 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 131-132)
    - Truman, Harry S., 1940 April 25 (Box 18, Folder 133)
    - United States Rubber Company, (*), 1946, 1952-1959 (Box 18, Folder 134)
    - W.J. Manufacturing Company, (*), 1956-1959 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - Warburg (Siegmund G.) and Company, (*), 1955-1960 (Box 19, Folder 136-150)
    - Willert, Sir Arthur, (*), 1948-1959 (Box 19, Folder 151-152)
    - Willis, Bickle, & Company, (*), 1946-1956 (Box 19, Folder 153-155)
    - Wiseman (Honor) Trust, (*), 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 156-158)
  - General Correspondence
    - A - B (Box 19, Folder 159-165)
    - C - Y, unidentified (Box 20, Folder 166-195)
  - Other Papers
    - Writings
      - "The Lion's Tale" (play): typescript and related correspondence, 1927-1929, undated (Box 21, Folder 196)
      - Description of Wiseman's last meeting with Woodrow Wilson (memorandum), 1928 July 3 (Box 21, Folder 197)
      - Letter to the editor of the New York Times, 1929 March 24 (Box 21, Folder 197)
      - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 198)
    - Personal financial papers, 1945-1959, undated (Box 21, Folder 199-206)
    - Memorabilia
      - Programs, invitations, etc., 1917-1961, undated (Box 21, Folder 207)
      - Guest-lists for dinners, luncheons, etc., 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 208)
    - Notebook of telephone numbers and addresses, undated (Box 21, Folder 209)
    - Printed matter, 1919-1959, undated (Box 21, Folder 210)
    - Photographs, 1938, undated (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - Biographical material, 1919-1957, undated (Box 21, Folder 212)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 21, Folder 213)